I'm Aaron Summer is here with the newest
Saints running back, Travis ETN. You are
from Jennings, Louisiana. How close is
this to the dream you had growing up?
>> I mean uh I I wouldn't say close dream I
had. I feel like it surpassed the dream
I had growing up. I mean uh just playing
in that stadium in Jennis, Louisiana uh
for four years. My goal was to get here
to play a championship game and I I
never got to accomplish that, but a guy
had bigger plans for me honestly. So,
uh, I'm just happy to be here and
excited to be able to chase a a a Super
Bowl in inside that stadium. And, man,
like I say, God has surprised my dreams
and I'm just grateful that I'm here.
>> Have you envisioned what it's going to
be like running into the Super Dome as
that being your home stadium?
>> Uh, no. I haven't envisioned I feel like
uh I I know it's going to be such a
special magical moment. Um, just like I
remember playing here um for the
national championship game when LSU won.
Uh, and and like just having that
Louisiana crowd that electric
electricity. I know it's going to be
just electric gonna be like just through
the roof whenever it happens. But I'm
gonna have to definitely slow down my
breathing kind of talk to myself so I
don't get overwhelmed with the moment.
But, uh, I'm just I just can't wait to
get there.
>> Your mom just got a house in Lafayette a
week ago and the the family is here in
Louisiana. What's the reaction been
like?
>> Oh, no, man. Uh, the family man,
everyone's just so ecstatic. Everyone's
just so happy. Uh, and like my mom,
she's just so grateful that she don't
have to drive now to see me no more. And
I'm grateful for her because I feel like
she has been with me throughout my whole
journey, uh, playing football since I
was in little league, just traveling
everywhere to see me. And for me to be
able to just pay her back by, uh, just
coming here, coming home and being able
to just just make it easier for everyone
and also myself and a great opportunity.
Uh, she don't have to travel around the
world to see me. And I I know that she
loves that. And she was been a Saint
fan. My grandma was a Saints fan. So my
whole family was a Saints fan. I didn't
even know there was any other NFL team
until I got older and start uh just
understanding football and things like
that. So, man, I just like this it just
I'm excited. Don't even really have the
words to say. I just kind of been all
processing it and just taking it all in
and just uh just grateful that I'm in
this moment.
>> When you look at what the Saints are
building here, they're investing around
their young quarterback and Tyler Shuck
and and what Kell Moore has done with
previous running backs and Saquon
Barkley in Philly. What does that say
about what you can do here and how much
are you looking forward to it?
>> I'm looking forward to it a lot and it
says the sky's is the limit. Uh but we
definitely know the work he had to put
in the work in first and I feel like uh
that's what I love about Kell just
talking to him yesterday and also
talking with Tyler uh he's already back
at it. So, uh, um, just being around a
bunch of guys who are humbled,
>> hung humbled and hungry, you know, and
want more. And I feel like we all like
we all in this phase of our career where
we want something, we got something to
prove. And, uh, Kell, he's been to the
top. So, he know what it takes. We have
a great leader in front of us. And, uh,
Tyler, he's a great leader as well. And
he's, he's he he he wants it. And, uh,
it's going to be easy to follow him. And
uh I'm just excited to come out here and
just just be all that I can be for them,
you know, and uh just help the team any
way that I can. Be selfless and uh great
things are going to happen for us.
>> Last year, you were only one of six
players in the league that had five or
more rushing touchdowns and five or more
receiving touchdowns. How do you build
off of that this next year?
>> Uh how you build off of it? Uh just just
just just get back to the basics, you
know. Uh just don't change anything I
did last year in the offseason. you
know, I feel like a lot of that comes
from just the work you put in uh when no
one's watching. So, I feel like just uh
being consistent in my work ethic. So,
whenever that time does come, I'm able
to rely on the things I built when no
one was watching. So, when the lights
come on, the moment isn't too bright for
me. And uh just being surrounded by
great guys and like you said, you got
Kellen, he's a great he's a great coach.
I feel he going to have great schemes
for us. And um he going to put us in
great place to make those plays. And uh
I just got to just go out there. I just
got to just do my work from here now and
uh just be patient and don't get too
excited because man after after just
being here just for two days man I'm
ready to go play right now. So but now
is the hard part is just uh being
patient and understanding that the real
work starts now. So just put myself in
position so whenever season come I'm in
great shape health and be able to be
there for my teammates.
>> As a person what kind of you have the
energy here. So what do you bring into
the locker room?
>> Uh bring to the locker room I feel like
I'm a guy who's who's seen it all. I've
been through the highs, the lows, the
ups and the downs. I feel like the the
NFL has twist and turned me each and
every way it could possibly possibly
could. So, uh I feel like I'm I'm open
to talk to any and everyone. Uh I I'm
I'm willing to give my advice. Uh I'm
willing to ask questions. So, I feel
like I'm a very like very chill guy,
very late, relaxed, but um when that
time comes and you know, we need to have
a serious conversation, I'm also there
for it. So, I feel like I'm going to
jail well with everyone. And especially
just talking with Tyler, talking with
Eric last night and Jawan. I feel like
we have a great group of guys in a great
a great core, a great nucleus, and we're
just going to keep expanding on that and
just just get everyone to buy in and
believe. You know, I feel like it all
starts with a belief system. And uh if
we get that, we have everything we need.
And uh we already know the city is going
to rally behind us.
>> All right, let's fast forward to the
season. What are the fans going to get
from you on Sundays?
>> Uh each and every Sunday, you're going
to get everything I have. uh each and
every Sunday, man. I feel like I just
like everything I got, you got, you
know? So, uh I'm just excited to be
there and I just can't wait to just, you
know, score that first touchdown for the
fans or uh get that first first down or
make that critical block. I mean, uh
it's nothing that I'm not willing to do
for the team. And uh at the end of the
day, it's all about the W. And uh as
long as we walk out with that W, uh no
one really cares how you got it. And
like uh my college coach always say, the
fun's in the winning. So, we want to get
back to that feeling or you get back to
chasing of those dreams and those goals
that we always had that got us here
>> and just take it one game at a time
because you can't go out there and like
like you say like we want to get to week
one but we had this process and steps we
got to take to get there. So, I mean uh
fans want to get everything I have each
and every Sunday. Uh guarantee that.
>> And you're going to have your son Saint
watching which I just love the name. It
worked out so perfectly.
>> Uh no, it it worked out perfectly. I
mean, uh, it it worked out perfectly
just to be here in this moment. Like,
that's something I couldn't dream. You
asked me earlier like,
>> well, uh, uh, is this what I dream?
Honestly, this surpass surpasses any
dream I could have ever dreamed, you
know, and I feel like that's why I just
keep falling back to God has a funny way
of humbling you. Like, uh, we all have a
plan. We all have a goal. We all have
things we want in life, but um, his plan
is so much much much better and ours.
And I'm just glad that I'm here a
walking testament just to let y'all
know, man, just never stop dreaming, you
know? Uh, and you can never dream too
big. And know when I'm walking out in
that stadium, I got my son, I got my
girl watching me. And uh, just just my
family, just everyone that I could have
ever hoped to be here in this moment is
here with me. And I'm grateful for that.
And that's the things that really
matter. And just having a community
that's going to rally behind us and
wants the best for us. Uh, that's all
you could ever ask for as a football
player, as a person, as a human, as in
in anything in life, you know, and uh,
just to have that and being here in this
moment. I mean, how can I not go out
there and give everything that I have uh
to to the New Orleans Saints?
>> You're gonna need a lot of tickets on
Sunday for all the people that are gonna
be coming here to watch you, and we
cannot wait to see it. Welcome to the
Saints. We're excited to have you.
>> Uh, thank you. Thank you for having me.
But, uh, I normally need a lot of
tickets, but I just want to let everyone
know tickets are not free [laughter]
and, uh, I can't just be handing them
out like that, you know? Like, there's
real life situations, too. Like, I have
a son. I have to take care of him. So, I
can't just be handing tickets to
everyone.
>> All right. Well, we'll work on that. But
thank you so much for
>> Thank you.
>> [clears throat]